TOMAS JIBAJA

WEB DEVELOPER





Links:

Portfolio LinkedIn GitHub FreeCodeCamp



Phone:

(549) 11-3677-7250



Mail:

tomasjibaja@gmail.com

SKILLS

HTML5
CSS3
JAVASCRIPT
React JS
Tailwind CSS
NEXT JS (in progress)
MFRN (in progress)

EDUCATION

FREECODECAMP

Responsive web design, 2022
Javascript algorithms and data structures, 2022
Front End development libraries, in progress

UNIVERSIDAD NACIONAL DE OUILMES

Bachelor's Degree, Music & Technologíes, 2020

PROFILE

I've completed my Bachelor's degree in Music & Technologies at UNQ in 2020 with a VR environment made with **Unity**, **PureData** and **C#** for thesis. Since then I've been dedicated to web development, specially Frontend due to my orientation.

I am determined to detail, user experience and high functionality.

I seek to be part of a team to which I can contribute my creativity, drive and selfdiscipline to enrich my experience, generate new links and feed my desire for constant learning.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE DEVELOPER

May 2022 - Present

Website and webapp design and development for entrepreneurs. Work available to check in my portfolio.

WEBMASTER - S&M BEAUTY

July 2023 - September 2023

Complete website refactoring to a new CMS (DriCloud)

WEBMASTER - CEAMA

March 2023 - May 2023

Wordpress website maintenance and refactoring

WEBMASTER - FESTIVAL DE LA GRATITUD

August 2022 - September 2022

Wordpress website maintenance and refactoring